<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KinesisPowersApp</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Type name...</string>
    //Categories
    <string name="Kinetics">Quinéticos</string>
    <string name="Extrasensorials">Percepción Extrasensorial</string>
    <string name="Magic">Magia</string>
    <string name="Various">Otros</string>
    // Psicokinesis
    <string name="aerokinesis_name">Aerokinesis</string>
    <string name="aerokinesis_definition">Consiste en la creación y dominio total del aire, esta es la más fácil
        de aprender después de la telekinesis. Los tres pasos o partes que la constituyen, son escalones
        muy grandes, y cada paso es más difícil que el anterior.</string>
    <string name="aerokinesis_exercise_1_name">Ejercicio 1 - Producción del Viento</string>
    <string name="aerokinesis_exercise_1_definition">Utilizaremos el Psi-Wheel (cuya construcción se explica en
        el tema de la Telequinesis), pondremos el Psi-Wheel delante nuestro pero no lo moveremos a través de
        los conocimientos telekineticos, nos soplamos en la palma de la mano y asimilamos esa sensación,
        extendemos nuestra mano de manera que la palma de la mano quede dirigida hacia el psi Wheel, y
        haremos notar la sensación de viento que producimos antes en nuestra mano, al principio sentirás
        una pequeña brisa, pero poco a poco esa sensación irá aumentando, y veras como el psi Wheel se
        mueve por el viento.</string>
    <string name="aerokinesis_exercise_2_name">Ejercicio 2 - Dominio del Viento</string>
    <string name="aerokinesis_exercise_2_definition">Dominar el viento es más difícil
        que producirlo, la mejor técnica de entrenar es coger una veleta de las que se ponen para
        indicar el sentido del viento, y que indique el sentido que tú quieras, para realizarlo haremos
        lo siguiente:
        Ponemos la veleta en la calle, ventana o cualquier sitio por el que pase el viento, ahora siente
        el viento y hazlo tuyo igual que con la psi Wheel, cuando lo sientas como parte de ti muévelo en
        el sentido que quieras, la veleta te servirá para saber si realmente el aire va hacia donde tú
        quieres.</string>
    <string name="aerokinesis_exercise_3_name">Ejercicio 3 - Oxigenación o Purificación del Aire</string>
    <string name="aerokinesis_exercise_3_definition">Esta parte necesita mucha paciencia, velas y un
        bote lo más grande posible. La oxigenación del aire es la inserción de oxígeno en un aire falto
        de este, sabemos que si falta oxígeno, no podemos mantener encendida una llama, pues
        intentaremos mantener una vela encendida en un lugar cerrado, la llama consumirá oxígeno,
        si este se agota la llama se apagará, si mantenemos la llama encendida quiere decir que
        estamos aportando oxígeno. Para mantenerla encendida:
        Primero de todo encender la vela, meterlo en el bote cerrado y cronometra el tiempo que tarda
        en apagarse. Metemos la vela en el bote, la encendemos, y sin cerrar el bote vamos
        visualizando como en la llama se mete oxígeno, lo puedes visualizar como aire azul, y expulsa co2,
        lo puedes visualizar como aire negro, cuando lo tengas asimilado tomate el tiempo necesario,
        entonces visualizamos como el co2 que expulsa la llama va cambiando de color y se
        va convirtiendo en aire azul (oxígeno), cuando estemos listos taparemos el bote sin dejar de
        visualizar ese cambio, cronometra sin dejar de visualizar el tiempo que tarda la vela en
        apagarse, si tarda mas es que vas bien, intenta mejor día a día el tiempo, hasta llegar al
        punto en el que no se desaparezca.</string>
    <string name="aerokinesis_exercise_4_name">Ejercicio 4 - Creación del Aire</string>
    <string name="aerokinesis_exercise_4_definition">La creación del aire es la parte más difícil,
        nos servirá para aumentar la presión en lugares cerrados:
        Llenamos un plato de agua, ponemos un trozo de corcho y encima de este le ponemos una
        vela pequeñita o un papel ardiendo, rápidamente lo tapamos con un vaso boca bajo,
        veremos como al consumirse el oxígeno el agua es absorbida por el vaso, pues ahora debemos
        sacarla aumentando la presión dentro del vaso:\n
        Visualizando un punto lleno de aire por ejemplo de color azul dentro del bote, que va
        aumentando de tamaño, el nivel de agua debe ir bajando, no desesperes si no lo consigues
        la primera vez, con la experiencia puedes ir probando a hinchar globos que están anudados
        ya aunque esto último es más difícil, ya que no puedes ver el interior del globo y es más
        difícil de visualizar.</string>
    <string name="atmokinesis_name">Atmokinesis</string>
    <string name="atmokinesis_definition">Is the ability to manipulate the atmosphere
        via psychic means. A user of this ability can change the weather and can cause freak weather.
        This ability allows manipulation and creation of natural weather conditions, such as, rain,
        thunderstorms, snow etc(…)\n
        Atmokinesis often comes with a psychic restriction preventing manipulation of anything other
        than weather and climate patterns, as the capability to generate holes in the ozone layer,
        or the like, would pose the possibility of bringing harm to the user.\n
        This ability might be connected with Aerokinesis (manipulation of air) the control of the
        wind, Electrokinesis (manipulation of electricity), described as the control of the lightning
        in the clouds, and Hydrokinesis (manipulation of water), through the various forms of
        precipitation (rain, snow, sleet, hail).</string>
    <string name="example">Esto es importante especialmente en las aplicaciones, estas deben empezar resolviendo
        UN SOLO problema y hacerlo muy bien, no trates de hacer una app “todóloga”, porque
        será confusa y mucho más difícil de hacer.
        • Inicia pensando en el problema, no en la solución, por ejemplo, no pienses en “Voy a hacer
        una app que ayude a las personas a reservar lugares en clubes nocturnos”, mejor piensa
        “¿Cuál es la parte más incómoda de ir a un club nocturno? Ah, tener que llamar antes para
        reservar, siempre olvido reservar”. Esto te guiará a brindar algo que la gente realmente
        quiera y/o necesite. Observa bien tu entorno para detectar problemas que puedas
        solucionar.
        • De preferencia (aunque no es obligación), crea un producto que resuelva un problema
        personal, algo que necesites pero que no exista o que en el mercado no sea lo
        suficientemente bueno todavía, esto te mantendrá enfocado en lograr tu objetivo, puesto
        que tu meta será solucionar algo que te beneficiará a ti también.
        • Si tu idea ya existe, no te desanimes, quiere decir que hay un mercado para ella.
        • Cuenta tu idea a amigos y personas que conozcas. Evalúa si realmente lo que tú crees que
        es un problema lo es o no. Importante, al menos al inicio NO PIDAS OPINIÓN DE TUS
        PADRES (Ellos siempre te dirán que la idea es buena o te dirán que te dejes de tonterías,
        pero digan lo que digan nublará tu punto de vista)
        1 Enfócate En Un Solo
        Problema y Resuélvelo
        Muy Bien
        2 Evalúa Tu Idea Con
        Personas Cercanas
        © 2017 JESUS ERNESTO VALDEZ ALMARAL, ALMARAL ENGINEERING
        • La opinión de tus amigos en general no es muy útil (O muy alentadores o muy negativos,
        no hay puntos medios), pero este ejercicio te dará un punto de partida y te ayudará a
        perder el miedo para entrevistar a desconocidos.
        • Crea una HIPÓTESIS acerca de tu producto y el problema que resuelve, por ejemplo: “El
        principal problema de ir a un club nocturno concurrido es tener que reservar con
        anticipación, mucha gente no lo hace por flojera o porque no le gusta contactar a otros
        para ese tipo de cosas”.
        • ESCRIBE UN CUESTIONARIO para que hagas las mismas preguntas a todos, el
        cuestionario te ayudará a conocer a tus futuros clientes, sus hábitos, sus problemas, y si tu
        hipótesis es real o solo está en tu mente. Guarda el cuestionario, lo necesitarás para
        después.
        • Puede ser tan sencillo como un bosquejo a mano en una libreta.
        • Muestra este prototipo a personas cercanas y a profesionales en desarrollo: diseñadores,
        programadores, etc. Esto, además de ayudar en la VALIDACIÓN de tu idea, te dará
        puntos de vista para saber si lo que quieres es realizable o no.
        • Una app muy buena para crear este tipo de prototipos es Pop (https://marvelapp.com/
        pop/), te ayudará a crear un prototipo en cuestión de horas o incluso minutos sin
        necesidad de programación.
        • Entrevista a unas 5 PERSONAS y haz mejoras, ITERA si es necesario y repite el proceso
        hasta que estés a gusto con tu idea.
        • Este es un prototipo un poco más detallado, creado con alguna herramienta de software:
        Powerpoint, Photoshop, Keynote, Sketch, etc.
        3 Crea Un Prototipo
        Básico
        4 Crea Un Prototipo
        Intermedio
        © 2017 JESUS ERNESTO VALDEZ ALMARAL, ALMARAL ENGINEERING
        • Este prototipo va dedicado a tus POSIBLES CLIENTES, ¡Sal a la calle a mostrarlo!
        • Si cuentas con una Mac, te recomiendo especialmente hacer prototipos con Sketch App
        (https://www.sketchapp.com/), es un software relativamente barato y enfocado al diseño
        de apps y páginas web, puedes probarlo por 30 días y ver si te convence.
        • Otro software que te recomiendo (y es gratis para realizar este paso) es InVision, te</string>

    <string name="claircognizance_name">Claircognizance</string>
    <string name="claircognizance_description">Is the ability for a person to acquire
        psychic knowledge without knowing how or why he or she knew it. The user can gain information about 
        a person, object, place, or event through intrinsic knowledge, as in it just comes to the users mind. </string>
    <string name="claircognizance_exercise_1_name">Exercise 1 - </string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    //DICTIONARY
    <string name="dictionary_word_1_name">AAAS</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_1_definition">Acronym for the American Association for the Advancement
         of Science (American Association for the Advancement of Science). Agency based in New
         York and that groups all the official sciences that exist in the world. In 1969, on proposal
         of the anthropologist Dr. Margaret Mead, parapsychology was accepted as science represented
         by the Parapsychologist Association, based on the quantitative studies carried out
         with the ESP phenomena carried out since 1927 by Dr. Joseph Banks rhine, in the Duke
         University, and those who later joined the research of PK (Psychokinesis).</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_2_name">Absent Healing</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_2_definition">Healing that takes place when the healer is not in direct
        contact with the person to be healed.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_3_name">Abracadabra</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_3_definition">Kabbalistic voice that constitutes the formula
         of magic expression to which extraordinary powers are attributed and which means
         "Divine Expression".</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_4_name">Tinnitus</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_4_definition">Ringing in the ears. Auditory sensations in
         absence of external stimulus. They can be interpreted as Paraphonic phenomena, voices
        from beyond the grave, etc.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_5_name"> Acupuncture</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_5_definition">Traditional Chinese medical practice that involves
        sticking needles into specific locations on the body.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_6_name">Adept</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_6_definition">Esoterically it is the name that is designated to the
        person who is initiated in the world of magical knowledge and has come to know
        and to master two hermetic secrets of esotericism. In Alchemy the term is used to
        designate the person who has reached the end of his work.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_7_name">Absent Sitter</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_7_definition">A person, not present during a sitting, on whose
        behalf readings are given. See also Proxy Sitting.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_8_name">Fortune telling</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_8_definition">Ability to foresee future events or
         discover hidden things by means of Extrasensory Perception (ESP) directly
         or using as clairvoyant support. Letters, crystal ball, coffee grounds,
         pendulum, etc.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_9_name">Advocation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_9_definition">System that consists of pronouncing a formula
         initiation by which a person declares himself a disciple and follower of an entity,
         teaching or hermetic philosophy.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_10_name">Aeromancy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_10_definition">Divinatory art based on the air that is breathed.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_11_name">Akashic Records</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_11_definition">"Memories" of all experiences since the beginning of time,
        believed by some mystical doctrines to be stored permanently in a spiritual substance (Akasha).</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_12_name">Agent</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_12_definition">Person who attempts to communicate information to
        another in an ESP experiment. The subject in a psychokinesis experiment. Person who is the
        focus of poltergeist activity.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_13_name">Soul</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_13_definition">Metaphysical essence of the human being that constitutes the
         Spiritual breath that activates the life of man. It is the Nephesh of the Hebrews and the Psyche
         of the Greeks.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_14_name">Alomancy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_14_definition">Synonym of saltiness. It is understood by saltiness,
         the divination by means of salt.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_15_name">Hallucination</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_15_definition">Perception of something that does not materially exist and
         that occurs in the subject by disturbance of the senses.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_16_name">Alien Abduction Experience</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_16_definition">Reported experiences of being abducted by alien creatures,
        often into spacecraft. Abductees often experience lost time and suffer loss of memory. When
        memories are recovered, often using hypnotic regression, abductees may report that surgical
        operations were performed on them. See also temporal lobe activity.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_17_name">Amnesia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_17_definition">Total or partial loss of memory.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_18_name">Angels</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_18_definition">Benevolent spiritual beings who help people in need.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_19_name">Artefact</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_19_definition">In parapsychology, false evidence of paranormal
        phenomena, due to some extraneous normal influence.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_20_name">Aquelarre</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_20_definition">Term derived from the basque voices Ake-Larren-Larrea,
         which means: meeting in the meadow of the goat. Witch meeting. Synonym of SABBAT. </string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_21_name">Aruspices</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_21_definition">Priests of ancient Rome whose mission consisted of
         predict the future through the viscera of the victims of the sacred sacrifices.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_22_name">Asynergy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_22_definition">Alteration of the faculty of association of movements
         elementals during the performance of complex acts.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_23_name">Asitism</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_23_definition">Voluntary fasting that lasts sometimes indefinitely,
         especially in acts of great mysticism.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_24_name">Aura</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_24_definition">Emanation generally colored, perceived by certain
         clairvoyants, around the human body and sometimes, around animals and plants.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_25_name">Spontaneous self-combustion</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_25_definition">See Biopirogenesis.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_26_name">Autohypnosis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_26_definition">Technique developed for the provocation of the hypnotic state
         produced by the individual himself. It is an autosuggestion.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_27_name">Self-description</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_27_definition">Notice that we receive, usually in dreams, from something
        that will happen to us.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_28_name">Autoscopy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_28_definition">Inner vision or ability to see one\'s own internal
        organs of the body.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_29_name">Autosuggestion</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_29_definition">Psychic phenomenon in which our imaginative mind
         creates a fixed idea that takes shape and settles in our psyche in the form of obsession, until
         become a subjective reality influencing our personality.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_30_name">Bicorporeity</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_30_definition">Synonym of Bilocation.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_31_name">Bilocation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_31_definition">Simultaneous presence of a person, in two different
         places. Parapsychology has shown that certain cases of bilocation are no more than
         cases of telepathy.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_32_name">Biofotogenesis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_32_definition">Modification of the cellular tissues of the human
        organism that causes them to emit flashes of light of their own.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_33_name">Biopause</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_33_definition">The ability to control and neutralize biological functions.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_34_name">Biopirogenesis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_34_definition">Biological self-production of fires in the person\'s own
         body who causes the combustion of the organism because of an internal ignition that
         manifested in the form of bluish flames that arise from the different natural orifices of the
         body and cause the Spontaneous Human Combustion (SHC).</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_35_name">Biotic</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_35_definition">Synonym for thelergy; physical energy.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_36_name">Astrology</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_36_definition">A theory and practice which attempts to identify the ways in
        which astronomical events are correlated with events on earth (e.g., with an individual\'s
        personality and biography, or with social and political trends).</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_37_name">Banshee</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_37_definition">In Gaelic belief, a female entity who heralds a death
        by groaning and screaming.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_38_name">Crystal ball</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_38_definition">Sphere or oval of crystal used in crystallomancy.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_39_name">Faraday camera</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_39_definition">It is a metal enclosure, cage or camera according to the
    uses, in which inside\'s electric or electromagnetic emissions can not penetrate. It was designed
    by the English physicist and chemist Faraday.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_40_name">PSI Field</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_40_definition">In addition to the gravitational, magnetic and electric fields
         the existence of a PSI field has been proposed internationally, which would explain the correlation between
         the physical factors that intervene in the paranormal (J.L. Jordán Peña).</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_41_name">Zener Cards</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_41_definition">Card game consisting of five different forms:
         star, circle, waves (three parallel wavy lines), square and cross; the game consists of
         25 letters. They were used by Dr. J.B. Rhine in his telepathy experiments and have
         become one of the most used instruments in scientific Parapsychology.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_42_name">Cartomancy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_42_definition">Divination of the future through cards or cards.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_43_name">Haunted House</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_43_definition">Popular name received by Poltergeist cases.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_44_name">Cataplexia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_44_definition">Physiological state of stupor motivated by fear that
         animals suffer because they have been placed in an unusual position in their usual way of
         life.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_45_name">Cenesthesia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_45_definition">The ability to provoke internal hallucinations in the
         own body. This phenomenon usually occurs in cases of possession in which cenesthetically
         the individual believes to be devoured internally by an "evil entity" and suffers the consequences
         as if the hallucinations were real.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_46_name">Cenesthetic</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_46_definition">Concerning the feeling experienced by the individual of
         his own existence.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_47_name">Chakras</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_47_definition">According to Eastern philosophy they are neuralgic centers of
         the person or spiritual energy points located in the astral body that have correlation
         in the center of the spinal cord and in the nerve plexuses of the human body.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_48_name">Kinetic</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_48_definition">Term that identifies the science of movements.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_49_name">Psychic Surgery</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_49_definition">Relative surgical technique that allows a healer,
         a gifted, to be able to surgically intervene any pathological alteration without any instrument.
         An example of this are the famous psychic operations that are carried out in the Philippines
         and in Brazil.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_50_name">Clairvoyance</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_50_definition">Natural or acquired psychic power to being able to see
         through dense matter without distance obstacles or time.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_51_name">Clariaudience</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_51_definition">Psychic ability to be able to hear at any distance,
         including ultraphysical sounds.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_52_name">Criptesthesia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_52_definition">Term devised by Charles Richet to designate the
         clairvoyance. At present it is in disuse.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_53_name">Cryptomnesia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_53_definition">Paranormal access to the depths of the subconscious,
         to evoke memories and subliminal perceptions that are contained there.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_54_name">Astral Body</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_54_definition">A term used by occultists, spiritualists and
        theosophists to refer to a supposed "double" of the person\'s physical body. The astral
        body is believed to be separable from the physical body during astral projection
        (out of body experience) and at death.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_55_name">Cumberlandism</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_55_definition">It consists essentially in perceiving unconscious
         movements of a subject whose thought one wants to know. It was presented for the first time
         by the English illusionist and conjuror Cumberland.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_56_name">Quackery</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_56_definition">Practice of curing diseases by no means
         approved by legal medicine. System used by those who say they have special
         faculties to cure physical ailments.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_57_name">Quack</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_57_definition">Sensitive subject with faculties that are on the margin
         of Biology, which can still diagnose a disease, how it can cure, or alleviate
         imposition of hands, by suggestion, prayers, etc. (In this field there is a lot of fraud).</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_58_name">Deja-Vu</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_58_definition">Traveling clairvoyance phenomenon whose etymology
         means "Already seen". It is created by neurological processes that produce a large
         intensification of consciousness, fact that provides the feeling of having been before
         in a certain place, perhaps in "another life", according to the followers of reincarnation\'s
        philosophy, based on the fact of prenatal awareness.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_59_name">Dermophilia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_59_definition">Appearance on various points of the skin, in
         sensitive individuals, of certain signs, spots or drawings of paranormal origin.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_60_name">Dermograms</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_60_definition">Graphics, symbols or drawings marked on the skin
         because of an epidermal irritation, caused almost always by the rupture of the capillaries.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_61_name">Dermooptic</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_61_definition">Capacity that some people have to be able to appreciate
         optical images through their skin, especially the fingertips.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_62_name">Splitting</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_62_definition">State of division of the personality. It is the faculty
         of being able to move our astral body, to act in a place far from the physical body.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_63_name">Diapsychia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_63_definition">Old denomination of the Telepathy.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_64_name">Charm</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_64_definition">A spell or object possessing magic power.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_65_name">Down Through</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_65_definition">Method of perception of Zener cards "down and through",
         used in ESP (Extra-Sensory Perception) in the quantitative experimentation of clairvoyance.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_66_name">Duke University</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_66_definition">Durham Study Center, North Carolina,
         United States of America (University) where the first official parapsychology
         laboratory was founded in 1930.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_67_name">Ecto-Coloplasmia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_67_definition">Modeling phenomenon of ectoplasm by means of the
         unconscious, forming figures, faces and various objects.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_68_name">Ectoplasia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_68_definition">Synonym of Telergy and Materialization. Term created
         by Myers in 1904 to define the materialized bioenergetic or teleneric substance.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_69_name">Ectoplasm</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_69_definition">Paranormal formation of a substance of unknown
         nature that usually emanates from the same mouth of the medium.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_70_name">Outpour</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_70_definition">Emanation of vitality attributable to the magnetism of
         body. Synonym for aura.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_71_name">Christian Science</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_71_definition">A religious healing movement founded by Mary Baker
        Eddy. Rejects orthodox medical practice.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_72_name">Automatic Writing</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_72_definition">Also called psychography; writing that some
         people in a semi-trance state can carry out, even being able to do foreign languages,
         totally unknown to the same subject.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_73_name">Eidetism</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_73_definition">Faculty that allows a subject to represent (by mnemic
         evocation) images with a high level of clarity or sharpness.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_74_name">Elohim</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_74_definition">God\'s proper name and for which he is still designated
         in Freemasonry.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_75_name">Escotography</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_75_definition">Proposed denomination for the photographic images
        printing phenomenon on sensitive emulsion, in the absence of light and without the aid of a camera or
         any optical device.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_76_name">ESP</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_76_definition">Abbreviation for Extra-Sensory Perception. In Spanish it is known
         by the initials P.E.S. o Extrasensory Perception.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_77_name">Spectrum</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_77_definition">Apart from its physical acceptance, which refers to a range of
         frequencies, is also used to designate an apparition or the phenomenon known as ghosts.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_78_name">Spiritualism</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_78_definition">Doctrine that starts from the basis of a philosophical
         scientific and moral background, that the human being is made up of three elements: body, spirit and a
         link called perispirit. Parapsychology studies spiritualism in depth, especially
         those mediums of physical effects.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_79_name">Spiritualists</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_79_definition">Relative to spiritualism.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_80_name">Stigmata</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_80_definition">Figurative or imitative skin signs that appear on
         the human body. They are alterations of psychosomatic character.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_81_name">Etrobia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_81_definition">Walk through the air Levitation of a person without
        human intervention.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_82_name">Exteriorization</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_82_definition">Simultaneous appearance of a person in two
         different places and at the same time.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_83_name">Extrasensory</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_83_definition">That goes beyond the physical senses.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_84_name">Extrasensory Faculties</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_84_definition">It refers to those faculties that allow us to enter
         in contact or being subjects of paranormal experiences, manifested through different ways to
         those of the physical senses.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_85_name">Fading</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_85_definition">Sudden phenomenon of the momentary disappearance of
         the radiesthetic effluvia.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_86_name">Ghosts</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_86_definition">Appearances, unfolding, bilocations, astral
         projection, etc. It can also be a telepathic hallucination as explained in almost all
         treatises of Parapsychology.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_87_name">PSI Phenomenon</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_87_definition">They are all the phenomena that occur as a result
         of the PSI action in all concepts. It covers all extrasensory perception C.E.S.P.
         Knowledge PSI-GAMMA and PSI-KAPPA.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_88_name">Physical phenomena</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_88_definition">Synonym for objective phenomena.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_89_name">Paranormal phenomena</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_89_definition">They are the usual, logical, whether psychological or
         physical, due to forces that seem intelligent, or to faculties unknown yet
         of the human mind.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_90_name">Objective Phenomena or PSI-KAPPA (PK)</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_90_definition">Are those phenomena of a paranormal nature manifested
         through effects of physical order: psychokinesis, ectoplasmia, psychophonies, etc.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_91_name">Subjective phenomena or PSI-GAMMA (PG)</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_91_definition">They are those phenomena of paranormal nature, manifested
         through effects of mental order, of our own psyche: telepathy, clairvoyance,
         precognition, etc.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_92_name">Fitomagnetism</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_92_definition">It is said of the magnetism of the vegetable kingdom.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_93_name">Fitometragraphy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_93_definition">Obtaining spiritual photographs of beings belonging
         to another dimension and photographs of the so-called astral body of people split into extracorporal
         experiences.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_94_name">Photoforia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_94_definition">This voice has been proposed for the genesis of paranormal light
         phenomena (bright flashes, bright spheres, etc.).</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_95_name">Photogenesis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_95_definition">Production of paranormal lights.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_96_name">Photopsia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_96_definition">Visual hallucination of elementary character. The subject perceives
         flashes of light or sees the whole field of vision dyed a single color.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_97_name">Unconscious Forces</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_97_definition">Potentials catalyzed by the medium in order to perform
         the proposed phenomenon.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_98_name">Geomancy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_98_definition">Divination procedure by examining the projecting
         figures formed on a table or a sieve, earth, dust, etc.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_99_name">Glossolalia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_99_definition">Phenomenon in which a medium under trance speaks or writes in a
         foreign language, which ignores in normal state.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_100_name">Gnosis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_100_definition">Phenomenon of acquisition of knowledge in a state of mysticism
         by ecstatic way, without mediating any intellectual or pedagogical system.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_101_name">Geoecia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_101_definition">Name by what is called Black Magic.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_102_name">Graphology</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_102_definition">Science that allows to determine the character, health,
         trends etc. of an individual, through the study of his writing.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_103_name">Grimoire</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_103_definition">Generic name of the book used by the Magi
         and occultists as a manual.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_104_name">Guru</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_104_definition">Spiritual instructor, also called master.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_105_name">Hagiography</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_105_definition">Studies made to the lives of the saints.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_106_name">Hematograms</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_106_definition">Strange drawings, symbols and graphics marked in the
         skin (or on canvases that have been attached to it) by blood effusion through
         the pores.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_107_name">Heteroscopy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_107_definition">GIt is usually an hallucination. In
         Parapsychology refers to the vision of the internal organs of another person.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_108_name">Hyaloscopy or Catopthomancy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_108_definition">Divinatory procedure by means of a
         crystal ball, mirror or any reflective surface.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_109_name">Hiloplasty</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_109_definition">Paranormal action that is characterized by
         materialization and dematerialization of physical bodies, which can thus penetrate
         hermetic enclosures.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_110_name">Hiloscopy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_110_definition">Voice proposed by Boirac for those
         paranormal phenomena in which matter interacts with the mind, as is the
         case of dowsing.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_111_name">Hyperacusis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_111_definition">Hyperesthesia limited to the perception of sounds.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_112_name">Hyperaphy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_112_definition">Tactile hyperesthesia, very marked epidermal sensitivity.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_113_name">Hyperesthesia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_113_definition">Unusual sensory acuity in special circumstances.
         The hyperesthetic perception in an amazing sharpness that can reach our normal sensations.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_114_name">Hypergeusia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_114_definition">Term referring to the hyperesthetic sensitivity to recruitment
         of gustatory stimuli.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_115_name">Hypermnesia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_115_definition">Phenomenon of exaltation of memory, produced in
         trance state and by hypermnesic persons with faculties to sharpen the psyche, up to
         remember with the most accurate details facts and knowledge lost in the memory of the
         time.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_116_name">Hipermnesoglosia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_116_definition">Capacidad de recordar, con todo su vigor primitivo,
        una lengua olvidada.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_117_name">Hyperosmia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_117_definition">Hyperesthetic sensitivity of subliminal olfactory
        uptake.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_118_name">Hypersensitive</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_118_definition">See medium, paragnosta, etc.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_119_name">Hypnosis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_119_definition">Provoked artificial dream. Suggestion and
         auto-suggestion are related to hypnosis, but without the subject having to be
         necessarily asleep.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_120_name">Hypnotism</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_120_definition">Set of phenomena that constitute hypnosis.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_121_name">Hipotaxic</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_121_definition">Semi-hypnotic state, technique similar to that of fascination.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_122_name">IAO</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_122_definition">Etymologically, breath of life.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_123_name">Ideofony</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_123_definition">Reception of music, bells, voices, noises,
         etc. without apparent cause and of paranormal origin.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_124_name">Ideoplasty</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_124_definition">Paranormal faculty attributed to thought and that
         exercises an action on the matter. They are forms of thought that sometimes
         impress, for example, sensitized photographic plates.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_125_name">Delusion</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_125_definition">False interpretation of a reality.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_126_name">Infestation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_126_definition">In houses or places. Synonym of poltergeist</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_127_name">Immortality</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_127_definition">Property that has a being to continue existing
         indefinitely, eternally, without corruption or death.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_128_name">Intuition</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_128_definition">Perception or instant knowledge of a truth
         or idea without the participation of any reasoning.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_129_name">Invocation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_129_definition">Any prayer is like an invocation.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_130_name">Jettatura</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_130_definition">Name given to malign influences or
         negatives produced through the look of the Sorcerer. Synonym of Evil eye.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_131_name">Ju-Ju</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_131_definition">Fetish name (amulet) used in the
         West African tribes.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_132_name">Kamarupa</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_132_definition">According to the Spiritualists, entity or operator,
         provocateur of incoherent and funny disorders in the course of sessions.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_133_name">Kappa</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_133_definition">In Parapsychology it is the term derived from
         Greek meaning "matter". See Psi-Kappa.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_134_name">Karma</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_134_definition">Absolute universal law of compensatory
        retribution between cause and effect based on the mechanism of action-reaction.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_135_name">Kinesis</string>
        <string name="dictionary_word_135_definition">Greek voice that means movement and in medicine
         it designates the action of the central nervous system manifested through the muscles. In
         Parapsychology is applied to the term Psychokinesia (Psycho-Kinesia) to define the group
         of paraphysical phenomena in which the mind inflicts dynamically on matter and
         it sets it in motion.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_136_name">Letargy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_136_definition">Continuous and pathological sleep.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_137_name">Levitation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_137_definition">Lifting of heavy objects in particular
         of the human body without intervention of any kind of force or physical agents.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_138_name">Lycanthropy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_138_definition">From the Greek Lycos, "wolf", and Anthropos, "man".
         Psychic disorder, a variety of zoanthropy, in which the patient believes he is a wolf.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_139_name">Litomagnetism</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_139_definition"> Magnetism that certain minerals possess and some
         precious stones</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_140_name">Litotelergy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_140_definition">Mysterious launch of stones in several
         directions without observable physical cause.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_141_name">Logurgy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_141_definition">Certain healers are considered to be loggis
         and surgeons who work by means of the power of the mind. Logurgy is in charge
         of study said phenomenology.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_142_name">Lucidity</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_142_definition">Popular term that indicates clairvoyance or telepathy.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_143_name">Mancies</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_143_definition">Divinatory techniques, some very ancient, most of them
         obtained by different means, such as: the crystal ball, the stripes of the hand,
         the letters, etc.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_144_name">Spiritualist Manifesto</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_144_definition"> Act by which the spirit reveals its presence.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_145_name">Materializations</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_145_definition">Synonym of ectoplasm. Alleged formations of
         isolated organs or complete beings, sometimes humanoids, animals, etc.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_146_name">Meditation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_146_definition">Mental process of reflection that allows through observation
         and analysis, knowing the essence of concrete things, or abstract speculation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_147_name">Medium</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_147_definition">mediumship</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_148_name">Mediumship</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_148_definition">Spiritualists consider medium to every person who in
         Trance state can communicate with spirits, which inhabit another dimension.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_149_name">Mind</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_149_definition">Intellectual power of the soul that encompasses the designs,
         the thought, the purposes and the will.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_150_name">Talking Table (Tiptology)</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_150_definition">Table normally tripod, used to obtain
         communications with the supraphysical world in the spiritualistic sessions.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_151_name">Metaphysics</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_151_definition">Part of philosophy, which deals with being as such,
         of its properties, principles and primary causes.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_152_name">Metagnomy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_152_definition">Synonym for clairvoyance.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_153_name">Touch Metagnomy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_153_definition">It is about supernormal knowledge through the
         touch. Synonym of Psychoscopy or psychometry.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_154_name">Metapsychic</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_154_definition">Science that studies all kinds of physical phenomena
         and psychophysicists who exceed the limits of normal consciousness due to the forces that
         seem intelligent or to unknown faculties of the mind. (Charles Richet).</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_155_name">Metasomoscopy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_155_definition">Faculty that have some sensitives that allow them to
         see inside the human body.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_156_name">Mimicry</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_156_definition">Property that some animals and plants possess
         to change shapes and colors resembling other beings, or certain inanimate objects
         among those who live.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_157_name">Monition</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_157_definition">Manifestation, generally vague and affective,
         of a paranormal awareness. It is a spontaneous extrasensory perception.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_158_name">Monoideism</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_158_definition">State of mind when it is occupied by a single idea.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_159_name">Pneumophonia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_159_definition">Phenomena of paraphonic character (emission of voices and musical
         melodies) that the spiritualists attribute to the direct action of the operators.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_160_name">Necromancy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_160_definition">Invocation to the dead to know the future, whatever
         the method is used.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_161_name">Nimbo</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_161_definition">Halo, fringe, circle or luminous crown, which surrounds
         the head of a divinity or saint.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_162_name">Evocative object</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_162_definition">It is the object that the sensitive one places between his hands
         or before his front, to give way to the manifestation of extrasensory perceptions in
         relation to it.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_163_name">Occultism</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_163_definition">Science, or school of thought, from the middle ages, that
         study the mysteries of nature at the same time as the psychic powers latent in the
         human being. In the popular language Occultism is equivalent to magic.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_164_name">Odic</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_164_definition">It is equivalent to energy, strength; with this term Baron Karl von
         Reichenbach (1788-1869) came to explain the existence of the human aura and some other psychobiological
         phenomena.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_165_name">Brain waves</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_165_definition">Electric rhythms generated in the nervous tissue of the brain.
         It has been classified into four ranges: Alpha of 8 to 12 cycles / second; Beta frequencies greater than 13
         cycles / second; Delta 1-4 cycles / second; and Theta of 4-8 cycles / second.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_166_name">Mental Waves</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_166_definition">Supposed waves emitted by the brain, constituted
         in the support of telepathic communications.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_167_name">Oniric</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_167_definition">It is said of how much it relates to dreams and
         certain imaginative situations of an unconscious nature.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_168_name">Oniromancy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_168_definition">Divination procedure through dreams.
         Art of knowing how to interpret dreams.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_169_name">Mental Orientation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_169_definition">In dowsing, orientation of the mind towards the
         object of the search or investigation.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_170_name">Osmogenesis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_170_definition">Production of aromatic substances of paranormal
        origin.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_171_name">Ouija</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_171_definition">Name derived from affirmative conjunctions
         of two languages: the French word Oui and the German Ja, both mean "yes". Is the
         instrument consisting of a circular "master" or small wooden board with mobility
         to move on a surface on which all the letters of the
         alphabet and numbers from 0 to 9 are.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_172_name">Sheeps</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_172_definition">EIn parapsychology it is the name given to the
         sensitive people who show a good predisposition to undergo the
         Experimentation ESP.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_173_name">Palingenesis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_173_definition">Regeneration, resurrection, reincarnation,
         transformation, renovation.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_174_name">Pandemonium</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_174_definition">This term defines the concrete fact in
         which an avalanche or set of noises is produced in a house at a certain time and
         that causes, suddenly, a total disorder in a mysterious way. The difference with the
         poltergeist, is that the Pandemonium has malefic character.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_175_name">Pantomnesia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_175_definition">It is said of the memory of the unconscious.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_176_name">Parabiothermia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_176_definition">Parabiological phenomenon that consists in controlling
         paranormally and at will body temperature.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_177_name">Paracardism</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_177_definition">Parabiological phenomenon that consists in controlling
         at will blood circulation and heart rate, at the precise moment.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_178_name">Parasciences</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_178_definition">Any field of human knowledge that try to
         analyze aspects of nature that are inaccessible to the current scientific method: like
         Parapsychology, Ufology, etc.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_179_name">Paragnosta</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_179_definition">It refers to a sensitive person who has
         an unusual capacity for extrasensory perception.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_180_name">Paranormal</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_180_definition">Term devised by W. Carrington to replace
         the supernormal term totally in disuse.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_181_name">Parapsicobiophysic</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_181_definition">Synonym term of parapsychology referring to
         the materialistic form of knowledge of paranormal phenomena, that from the
         agnostic perspective, is studied in some Eastern European countries.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_182_name">Parapsychology</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_182_definition">According to Dr. J. B. Rhine, Parapsychology is
         the branch attached to psychology, and deals with studying psychic, psychophysical, and
         paraphysicians. Parapsychology is the branch of knowledge that investigates those
         interrelationships between man and his means: biological, physical, and social.
         (Currently it is also called Parapsicobiofísica).</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_183_name">Paratherapy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_183_definition">Any phenomenon that is linked to the
         healers, psychic surgeons, etc.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_184_name">Radiesthetic pendulum</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_184_definition">Species of plumb or metal pendulum used
         by the dowser to find what you are looking for.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_185_name">Extrasensory perception (ESP)</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_185_definition">External fact without the intervention of any
         meaning known or conceivable. It is what the human being captures or receives through
         sensory channels or abnormal senses. In English E.S.P. (extra sensory perception).
         English acronyms are accepted throughout the world and are usually never translated.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_186_name">Pyromancy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_186_definition">Divination by means of fire.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_187_name">Pyrovasia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_187_definition">Faculty that certain people have to walk
         barefoot on the embers.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_188_name">P.K. (PSI-KAPPA)</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_188_definition">Psychokinesis. It is the direct influence exerted
         by a subject on a physical system without intervening instrument or physical energy
         known or conceivable.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_189_name">Pneumotofony</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_189_definition">Oral communication, of the spirits without the
         intervention of the voice of the medium.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_190_name">Pneumatography</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_190_definition">Direct writing of the spirits without the
         intervention of the medium's hand.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_191_name">Poltergeist</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_191_definition">An exclusively parapsychological term that corresponds
         to the German voice that means: "noisy elf". It is called like this to a wide range of
         Paraphysical phenomena (rarely parabiological) that are always linked to
         a place (homes, cemeteries, temples, etc.). Some of the facts registered in
         this type of manifestation have been: Litotelergy, Raps, Teleplasties, Telekinesis of
         furniture or heavy objects, ghosts, voices and paranormal noises. They seem to associate
         to the presence is a sensitive, often in adolescent age. They have also received
         the name of haunted houses or infestation.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_192_name">Postcognition</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_192_definition">Synonym of retrocognition. Perception of
         past events.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_193_name">Precognition</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_193_definition">Paranormal perception of an event that
         has not happened yet.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_194_name">Premonition</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_194_definition">Vague warning, generally, regarding the
         future or a future event.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_195_name">Coven</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_195_definition">A group of witches.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_196_name">Psychobulia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_196_definition">Unconscious capacity that has a gifted to
         intelligently directing his telergy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_197_name">Psychokinesis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_197_definition">Alleged action of the mind on a physical
         evolution system.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_198_name">Psychophonies</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_198_definition">Recordings on virgin tape in any tape recorder,
         or any other type of magnetic or optical support, of human voices, whispers, noises, music,
         bells, etc. of ignored origin. (Also called Paraphonies). Although the distinction between
         the terms paraphonies and psychophonies is practically null, the most appropriate name for the
         The phenomenon would be the paraphony.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_199_name">Psychography</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_199_definition">Appearance of a writing on a blackboard, wall, paper,
         etc. that could not be done by normal methods. It is of paranormal origin.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_200_name">Psychometry</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_200_definition">Synonym for psychoscopy. In parapsychology this
         term is used to designate the E.S.P. that some sensitive people have while
         hold in their hands any object that has belonged to the person he is looking for.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_201_name">Psychorrhagia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_201_definition">Liberation of telergy or of certain energies and
         unconscious forces.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_202_name">Psychoscopy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_202_definition">Clairvoyant faculty that possess some sensitive,
         that having a witness in your hands, such as a handkerchief, a pen, etc., will make them relate
         mentally with the owner of that object and you will obtain the necessary information.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_203_name">Psychotronics</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_203_definition">Synonym of Parapsychology; term used
         in the old socialist or communist countries.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_204_name">Quirology</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_204_definition">Art of knowing the character of a person by the
         observation of their hands.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_205_name">Palmistry</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_205_definition">It is a divinatory art through study
         or analysis of the stripes of the hand, according to universally accepted rules.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_206_name">Rabdomancy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_206_definition">It is divination by means of a stick or cane.
         It is of ancient origin and is the forerunner of modern Dowsing.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_207_name">Radiation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_207_definition">Energetic emissions that can have oscillatory nature.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_208_name">Dowsing</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_208_definition">It is the art of catching by means of a rod or
         pendulum, springs, treasures, things buried, lost, etc. this is due to
         the extrasensory perception of the individual.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_209_name">Raps</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_209_definition">English word that designates unusual noises
         that occur without explainable cause.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_210_name">Reincarnation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_210_definition">According to Spiritism and many religions,
         return of the spirit to bodily life; plurality of existences.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_211_name">Retrocognition</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_211_definition">Knowledge of past events or experiences
         out of the memory of the individual and that could not be known by the normal sensory
        channels.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_212_name">SEIP</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_212_definition">Acronyms of the Spanish Society of
         Parapsychological Investigations. This society is chaired by Pedro Amorós
         (Researcher in Instrumental Transcommunications) and is based in Alicante (Spain)
         and its research field is international.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_213_name">Sematology</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_213_definition">Synonym of tiptology.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_214_name">Sensitive</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_214_definition">Person who has special faculty to
         experience an infinity of paranormal phenomena.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_215_name">Simulation</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_215_definition">Many paranormal phenomena can be simulated
         or tricks.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_216_name">Mystical Sounds</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_216_definition">Certain sounds perceived during the
         meditation.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_217_name">Telepathic suggestion</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_217_definition">Telebulia, transmission of the will at a distance.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_218_name">Takinesis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_218_definition">Fast, close movements of various objects
         produced by the medium.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_219_name">Tarot</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_219_definition">Deck composed of 78 cards of Egyptian origin and that
         are used for prediction.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_220_name">Telebulia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_220_definition">It is said of the telepathic suggestion.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_221_name">Telekinesis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_221_definition">Displacement of objects without observable physical cause
         or known.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_222_name">Telehypnosis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_222_definition">Hypnotic induction from a distance.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_223_name">Telepathy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_223_definition">Transmission of thought at a distance.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_224_name">Teleplasty</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_224_definition">Synonym of ectoplasmia. Objectivation of forms.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_225_name">Telergy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_225_definition">Physical or psychophysical force put into play in
         many acts of telepathy.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_226_name">Curse</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_226_definition">Words spoken or written in order to influence others
        paranormally, causing them harm.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_227_name">Termogenesis</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_227_definition">Energy causing and responsible for fires within
a house, business, office, etc. usually caused by the telergy.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_228_name">Witness</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_228_definition">In dowsing, body of the same nature as the wanted.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_229_name">Tiptology</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_229_definition">Means of communication of the spirits by means of
         percussions or blows, sometimes imperfect, due to its slowness.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_230_name">Emptying</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_230_definition"> Molds representing hands and arms obtained on
         paraffin, clay or any other plastic substance and whose formation has been achieved
         always in a totally paranormal way.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_231_name">Dowsing Rod</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_231_definition">They are two rods of flexible material, joined by
         an end and whose function is to amplify and make sensitive the unconscious movements
         of the hands, in its precise moment, in the course of the dowsing investigations.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_232_name">Foretell</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_232_definition">Predict.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_233_name">Clairvoyant</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_233_definition">In parapsychology a clairvoyant is a person with
         faculties of proven clairvoyance.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_234_name">Xenoglossia</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_234_definition">Locution of foreign languages that were never learned.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_235_name">Xilomancy</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_235_definition">Divination made by means of wood.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_236_name">Dowser</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_236_definition">It is said of the person with faculties for dowsing.
         The people trained to locate groundwater wells were commonly known.
         Old name for the dowser, now completely obsolete.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_237_name">Zener</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_237_definition">Name by which the letters called
         PES in the statistical analysis of certain extrasensory perception phenomena.</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_238_name">Zombie</string>
    <string name="dictionary_word_238_definition">A corpse that has been partly brought back
        to (soul-less) life by magic.</string>
</resources>
